<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./Herb Fargus.png</path>
    <name>Herb Fargus</name>
    <image>./Herb Fargus.png</image>
	<desc>   Herb Fargus is one of the main developers for RetroPie and on this channel from time to time interesting and useful information as well as tutorials are shared.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./skyscraper git hub.png</path>
    <name>skyscraper git hub</name>
    <image>./skyscraper git hub.png</image>
	<desc>Skyscraper by Lars Muldjord

A powerful and versatile yet easy to use game scraper written in C++ for use with multiple frontends running on a Linux system. It scrapes and caches various game resources from various web sources, including media such as screenshot, cover and video. It then gives you the option to combine all of these resources into the most complete results by using the provided 'localdb' scraping module. And the best part is it is built into this image!! SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./RGT 85.png</path>
    <name>RGT 85</name>
    <image>./RGT 85.png</image>
	<desc>  RGT 85 brings the best content in the world of retro gaming with a dash of modern gaming thrown in.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./DOS Nostalgia.png</path>
    <name>DOS Nostalgia</name>
    <image>./DOS Nostalgia.png</image>
	<desc>  This channel is dedicated to the good old days of PC gaming when MS-DOS was in its prime. Stay tuned for nostalgic reviews of some well known PC titles as well as some forgotten ones.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Retro Arena git hub.png</path>
    <name>Retro Arena git hub</name>
    <image>./Retro Arena git hub.png</image>
	<desc>Retro arena git hub is full of usefull information about retropie on the Odroid Xu4.   
SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Q bertaddict.png</path>
    <name>Q bertaddict</name>
    <image>./Q bertaddict.png</image>
	<desc>Opensource Gaming, Reviews, Gameplay, and Pickups Videos are what you will find here. Q is one of the latest and most welcome additions to the team he brings a wealth of knowledge and all around love for retrogaming and the retrogaming community. Be sure to check out his channel as there are a ton of videos on the ORA retropie build. SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Blue Television Games.png</path>
    <name>Blue Television Games</name>
    <image>./Blue Television Games.png</image>
	<desc>  A family friendly channel that features lots of Super Mario Maker videos as well as retro games, indie games, and more. Stop by for showcases, unboxings, playthroughs, live streams, reviews, tutorials, and other gaming videos.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./MickMake.png</path>
    <name>MickMake</name>
    <image>./MickMake.png</image>
	<desc>  The goal of this channel is to educate and inspire the electronics ProMaker, Maker, or someone starting. Whether you're into STEM, Internet of Things, makerspaces, Maker Faires, quick tutorials, projects or just an honest review on a Maker product then this channel is for you.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Simply Austin.png</path>
    <name>Simply Austin</name>
    <image>./Simply Austin.png</image>
	<desc>The Simply Austin Channel is a unique blend cutting edge video tutorials on some of the most entertaining systems and programs out there.SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Larry Bundy Jr.png</path>
    <name>Larry Bundy Jr</name>
    <image>./Larry Bundy Jr.png</image>
	<desc>  Want to know obscure gaming facts you've never heard before? Then Check them out!!! Obscure games, movies and a bizarre sense of humour!!! Was the TV personality That Guru Larry.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Cygnus Destroyer.png</path>
    <name>Cygnus Destroyer</name>
    <image>./Cygnus Destroyer.png</image>
	<desc>  Home of The LJN Defender & Innocent Until Proven Guilty, as well as Cygnus Destroyer Reviews, Top 10s, & ROM Hack/fan game specials. Good, bad, and in between...They cover it all in the realm of video games, and they give even the worst of offenders a fair shake.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./The Retro Arena.png</path>
    <name>The Retro Arena</name>
    <image>./The Retro Arena.png</image>
	<desc>This is our youtube channel  Host and founder Adrian Tauer gives you the latest and greatest on the inner workings, progress and developement. Be sure to subscribe to stay up to date. SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ETA prime.png</path>
    <name>ETA prime</name>
    <image>./ETA prime.png</image>
	<desc>A man who really needs no introduction ETA Prime is one of the most well know names in the emulation scene with a impressive collection of videos tutorials and how to videos on everything from pc to arcade machines to SBC's Be sure to check this link out. SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Floob.png</path>
    <name>Floob</name>
    <image>./Floob.png</image>
	<desc>  Retrogaming channel, especially with info on Raspberry Pi and RetroPie.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./8 Bit Flashback.png</path>
    <name>8 Bit Flashback</name>
    <image>./8 Bit Flashback.png</image>
	<desc>Be sure to check out 8bit's channel for some in game testing of the image as well as some pretty cool projects he has done with the Xu4. SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ExplainingComputers.png</path>
    <name>ExplainingComputers</name>
    <image>./ExplainingComputers.png</image>
	<desc>  ExplainingComputers uploads weekly computing videos. It is produced by Christopher Barnatt, who spent 25 years teaching computing and future studies in the University of Nottingham.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Level Up.png</path>
    <name>Level Up</name>
    <image>./Level Up.png</image>
	<desc>  They make 8-Bit Video Game Animations! Their dream is to be one of the most well known and best Sprite Animators on YouTube!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./HistoricNerd.png</path>
    <name>HistoricNerd</name>
    <image>./HistoricNerd.png</image>
	<desc>  	A Channel that follows the influence of history in gaming. Also really random reviews.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Nostalgia Nerd.png</path>
    <name>Nostalgia Nerd</name>
    <image>./Nostalgia Nerd.png</image>
	<desc>  
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./John Hancock.png</path>
    <name>John Hancock</name>
    <image>./John Hancock.png</image>
	<desc>  	Longtime collector and gamer who plans on opening a future video game museum in the Northwest. Focused on preserving physical copies of video games as well as consoles and to showcase collection, product reviews, video games news, as well as live streaming games with commentary weekly. Completed 28 North American video game sets and plans on getting more.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./SuperDerek RPGs.png</path>
    <name>SuperDerek RPGs</name>
    <image>./SuperDerek RPGs.png</image>
	<desc>  If you're a fan of RPGs then you should be watching SuperDerek RPGs, where they'll help you find your next favorite! Three new videos each week covering everything from RPG news, first-impressions reviews and more! Covering everything from Retro Turn-Based RPGs to new Western Action-RPGs.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./This Does Not Compute.png</path>
    <name>This Does Not Compute</name>
    <image>./This Does Not Compute.png</image>
	<desc>  They create videos about retro video games and technology, product reviews, DIY projects and content creation. In their weekly podcast series you'll find some deeper conversations about how all this technology impacts us.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Spawn Wave.png</path>
    <name>Spawn Wave</name>
    <image>./Spawn Wave.png</image>
	<desc>  We love video games, TV shows, Movies and all other types of media. Check out our videos and have fun on our channel!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
   <game>
    <path>./sudo mod website.png</path>
    <name>SudoMod Website</name>
    <image>./sudo mod website.png</image>
	<desc> Sudomod is A community for people who like to make cool stuff using Odroid, Raspberry Pi, Arduino, various single board computers, and retro game consoles.SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
   <game>
    <path>./sudo mod youtube.png</path>
    <name>SudoMod YouTube</name>
    <image>./sudo mod youtube.png</image>
	<desc> Sudomod is A community for people who like to make cool stuff using Odroid, Raspberry Pi, Arduino, various single board computers, and retro game consoles.Here is a link to their YouTube channel.SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./8bitguy.png</path>
    <name>8bitguy</name>
    <image>./8bitguy.png</image>
	<desc>  A computer video series focusing mainly on retro technology from the 80's, 90's and 2000's. However, once or twice a year they'll create something totally out there.  Their main goal at this point is to make educational content about retro technology that is interesting and engaging.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./ORA FAQ.png</path>
    <name>ORA FAQ</name>
    <image>./ORA FAQ.png</image>
	<desc>Frequently Asked Questions,Probably one of the most important links it will answer a good percentage of your questions right off the bat.It is highly recomended you look here first. If you cant find the answer to your question here we are available on Facebook or Discord. This is also a link to our website where you will find all sorts of info and downloads to make your Odroid Retropie experience even better! SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Modern Vintage Gamer.png</path>
    <name>Modern Vintage Gamer</name>
    <image>./Modern Vintage Gamer.png</image>
	<desc>  They love Modern, they love Retro. Tech, Hardware, Gaming.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./release notes.png</path>
    <name>release notes</name>
    <image>./release notes.png</image>
	<desc>Release Notes (Which we highly encourage you to download as they provide valuable information to include the login credentials.SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./The RA Patreon.png</path>
    <name>The RA Patreon</name>
    <image>./The RA Patreon.png</image>
	<desc>We hope you are enjoying The RA build. Its only possible with our stong community If you are already a patron we thank you.If not please consider supporting this great project.SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Cinemassacre Plays.png</path>
    <name>Cinemassacre Plays</name>
    <image>./Cinemassacre Plays.png</image>
	<desc>  This is Cinemassacre's second Youtube channel. Mainly uploads of live streams. You can also find James older projects and AVGN episodes in higher quality. If you want to see their scripted content, visit their main channel.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./LGR.png</path>
    <name>LGR</name>
    <image>./LGR.png</image>
	<desc>  Lazy Gaming Reviews sports over 1 million followers with Classic computer gaming, Oddware, thrifting, Tech Tales, Sims, etc. Weekly coverage of retro tech, PC games, and more!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gamester81.png</path>
    <name>Gamester81</name>
    <image>./Gamester81.png</image>
	<desc>  A channel where Gamester81 reviews retro and obscure consoles, video games, home brew games and more!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Cinemassacre .png</path>
    <name>Cinemassacre </name>
    <image>./Cinemassacre .png</image>
	<desc>  Cinemassacre Productions! Bringing you many different gaming related web series including: Angry Video Game Nerd, Mike Matei Game Videos, Rental Reviews and more!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Game Sack.png</path>
    <name>Game Sack</name>
    <image>./Game Sack.png</image>
	<desc>  They're Joe and Dave. We talk about video games we find interesting and a few that may not be so great.  Long new episode every other Sunday released at 12:00am mountain time (US).
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./CGQ.png</path>
    <name>CGQ</name>
    <image>./CGQ.png</image>
	<desc>  Classic Gaming Quarterly attempts to offer an alternative to the low-effort, cookie-cutter, "me too" content flooding the gaming genre on YouTube. They attempt to make higher-effort, higher-quality, family-friendly content, and hopefully by watching their show you'll learn something new about your favorite video games.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Eazy Hax.png</path>
    <name>Eazy Hax</name>
    <image>./Eazy Hax.png</image>
	<desc>A channel about....Well...easy hacks.... I fix a TON of stuff. Everything from smart phones, old radios, old retro gaming consoles to old flickering LCD Screens (curb rescues). Hacking old consoles, phones, whatever! I also know A LOT about Linux. I have been working with it professionally and personally for over 17 years and it just happens that is exactly what retropie runs on. I decided to make a channel dedicated to all the stuff I have learned....given that at least some of it came from other youtubers. Thanks for watching and I hope at least one of the videos helps you out of a bind! -Forrest. SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Gaming Historian.png</path>
    <name>Gaming Historian</name>
    <image>./Gaming Historian.png</image>
	<desc>  The Gaming Historian is a documentary series all about the history of video games. They also like to review books and certain games that they find interesting.
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Novaspirit Tech.png</path>
    <name>Novaspirit Tech</name>
    <image>./Novaspirit Tech.png</image>
	<desc>  They are a Avid Thinker, 3D Printing, Single Board Computer Programmer, Web evangelist, Hacking and Breaking expert, Problem Solver, Technology Obsessed, Gamer, Coffee lover!
   SCAN BARCODE WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE TO ACCESS LINK.</desc>
  </game>
</gameList>
